ひょんなことから
働くことになった➡
その名は 坂田 銀時｡
…って そんなｱﾆﾒだっけ？＞
ﾎﾞｸ 志村 新八と 神楽ちゃん｡
侍は 衰退の一途をたどっていた｡
甘党 ｱﾝﾄﾞ 無鉄砲な
この男の営む 万事屋で➡
ﾎﾞｸら万事屋３人で
腐った江戸を 一刀両断！
そんな時代に
侍魂をもった男がひとり｡
(新八)＜侍の国… ﾎﾞｸらの国が
そう呼ばれたのは 今は 昔の話｡
20年前 突如 宇宙から舞い降りた
天人の台頭と 廃刀令により➡
The land of the samurai.
There was a time, long ago, when our country was called by that name.
With the arrival of the "Amanto" from outer space
and the Sword Ban twenty years ago, the samurai class fell into decline.
In such hard times, there was one man left with the spirit of the samurai.
His name is Gintoki Sakata, a reckless Jack of All Trades with a sweet tooth.
Due to some rather unexpected events, I, Shinpachi Shimura, ended up working here.
The three of us slice up a corrupt Edo.
Wait, is that really the story?
[Suspected for the bombing, the Odd Jobs gang are under police questioning.]
[By the way this man is the "Boss", and he's holding a glass of brandy.]
♪♪『お前の父ちゃん ××』
["Keep Your Promise Even If It Kills You"]
[Oedo Police Station]
(銀時)おいおい
いいかげんにしてくれよ｡
Hey, hey, enough already.
ｵﾚたちゃ無関係だって
100万回も言ってんだろ｡
We had nothing to do with it, I'm telling you.
I've told you that a million times.
Some things never change.
(警官)今も昔も変わらないんだよ｡
犯人にかぎって➡
It's always the perpetrator who claims he had nothing to do it.
ｵﾚは無関係だ とか
濡れ衣だ とかな｡
(銀時)ｱﾝﾀ 何回 聞いてんだ！
How many times are you going to ask me?
最初から最後まで
全部 説明しただろうがよ！
I've explained everything from the very beginning to the very end.
Yeah, yeah. All the guilty ones say that.
(警官)はいはい
犯人は みんな そう言うの｡
ｳﾁの子にかぎって とか
記憶にございません とか｡
"My kid would never do that," or "I don't remember."
そういうこと言ってるﾔﾂの言葉と
同じくらい 信じられないだろ？
You're just as hard to believe as the people who say those things, don't you think?
早く吐いちまいなよ｡
Come on, confess already.
こっちも 慈善事業やってんじゃ
ないんだから｡
We're not running a charity here, you know.
それとも ｱﾝﾀら なに？
Or is it that you guys think you'll get off if you keep holding out on us?
(警官)粘り続けりゃ
なんとかなると思ってるの？
そりゃ 無理な話だって｡
Ain't gonna happen.
I've had enough, you shithead!
いいかげんにしろや
このｸｿﾎﾞｹ!!
えぇ～!?
We're telling you, we're innocent!
(新八)こっちは 無実だって
言ってんだよ！
うだうだ言ってねえで
今すぐ ここから出せや!!
Quit wasting your breath and let us out of here right now!
こっちは 行かなきゃいけねえ所が
あんだよ！
We have places to go!
Violent Four-Eyes.
(神楽)ﾊﾞｲｵﾚﾝｽ ﾒｶﾞﾈ…｡
おい ｷｬﾗ変わってんぞ｡
Hey, his personality is changing!
ｹｯ！ 命 張って
爆弾 処理してやったのによ➡
I risk my life getting rid of that bomb and they rake me over the coals for three days.
３日も 取り調べなんざ
しやがって… 腐れ外道が！
Rotten cops!
もういいじゃないですか｡
I think you've kept us long enough.
Thanks to me, at least we're not on their most wanted list anymore.
ﾎﾞｸのおかげで
容疑も晴れたことですし｡
But why'd they release us after Shinpachi freaked out like that?
っていうか… なんで
新八が ﾄﾞｽをきかせたくらいで➡
釈放なんだ？
ふだん おとなしいﾔﾂのほうが➡
Because they know someone normally docile is more difficult to deal with when they crack under the pressure.
ｷﾚたら
始末に悪いの 知ってるｱﾙよ｡
どうも ｽｯｷﾘしねえ｡
They piss me off.
ｺﾞｰﾙﾃﾞﾝｳｫｰﾀｰ かけていこう｡
よっしゃ ｱﾀｼ ｹﾞﾛ吐いちゃるよ｡
So piss on them.
Okay, I'll puke on 'em.
やめろ～っ！
ﾃﾚﾋﾞなんだから 我慢しろって!!
Stop that! This is TV! Control yourselves!
ｱﾝﾀらに かまってたら
何回 捕まっても ｷﾘないよ｡
There'll be no end to the number of times I'll be arrested if I hang around you guys.
ﾎﾞｸ 先に帰ります！
I'm going on home!
ちゃんと
まっすぐ 家 帰れよ ﾊﾞｶｺﾝﾋﾞ！
Don't get lost on the way home, you morons!
おいおい ﾂｯｺﾐいなかったら
このｱﾆﾒ 成立しねえぞ｡
Hey, hey, we can't have an anime without a straight man.
しゃあねえなぁ 今週は ｵﾚが➡
I don't have a choice then.
I'll be the straight man this week.
ﾂｯｺﾐで いくか…｡
(吐く声)
You...watch where you're puking!
お前！
どこに ｹﾞﾛ吐いて… くさっ!!
Whadda stench!
ん？
(親父)はぁっ！
(親父)だぁっ！ …ぐぇっ！
(親父)ｲﾀﾀﾀ… それに くさっ！
Whadda stench!
(警官)お～い！ ｿｲﾂ 止めてくれ！
脱獄犯だ！ くさっ!!
Hey...
Stop him! He's an escaped convict.
Phew!
はい？
Yes?
ﾁｯ…｡
Stand back!
(親父)来るんじゃねえ！
この ｹﾞﾛ娘が➡
Don't you care what happens to barf babe here?
どうなってもいいのかぁ!?
(警官)貴様！
You scum!
ｸｯ 今日だけは…｡
Just for today, I'm...
おい そこの天然ﾊﾟｰﾏ！
Hey you, with the naturally wavy hair.
(親父)車の運転できるか？
あぁ｡
Can you drive a car?
Yeah.
えぇい！ お上に盾ついて
ﾀﾀﾞで済むと思うのか!?
Damn it! Do you think you can get away with defying the law?!
(神楽)あぁ～っ！
He's got me!
捕まっちゃったｱﾙよ｡ 怖いｱﾙよ｡
I'm scared.
これは 言うこと聞くしかねえな｡
I have no choice but to do as he says.
(親父)ｵﾗｵﾗ どけどけ！
Come on, come on, outta my way.
♪♪～
(警官)ｸｯ…！
After him! Don't let him get away!
追え！ 絶対に逃がすな!!
まっ ぶっちゃけ
ｽｶｯとしたけどさぁ➡
Well, that was exhilarating.
こんなことして
ﾎﾝﾄに 逃げ切れると思ってんの？
But do you really think you can get away with this?
いいから 右 曲がれ｡
Never mind. Just turn right.
今どき 脱獄 完遂するなんざ➡
These days, escaping from prison is tougher than winning the lottery.
宝ｸｼﾞの１等 当てるより
難しいって｡
I have no intention of getting away for good.
逃げ切るつもりなんてねえ｡
Just for today.  I'll be happy if I can be free for just one day today.
今日一日だ｡ 今日一日
自由になれれば それでいい｡
♪♪～
Today, is a special day.
(親父)特別な日なんだ… 今日は｡
特別な日ねぇ｡
A special day, eh?
If you're captured immediately after breaking out of prison,
確かに
脱獄して すぐに捕まりゃ➡
一生 忘れられない特別な日に
なりそうだけどな｡
it'll be a special day you'll never forget for the rest of your life.
(ﾊﾟﾄｶｰのｻｲﾚﾝ)
Step on it! I can't get caught now!
飛ばしてくれ！ 今 ｵﾚは
捕まるわけにはいかねえんだ!!
仰せのとおりに！ ﾌﾞｰｽﾄ!!
As you wish. Boost!
♪♪～
I'm a new teahouse maid, sir.
(ﾒｲﾄﾞ)新しくできた
ﾒｲﾄﾞ茶屋です ご主人様～｡
(山田)萌え～｡
(ﾊﾟﾄｶｰのｻｲﾚﾝ)
So cute.
Move, move, move!
どけどけ どけ～!!
(警官)止まれ ﾊﾞｶ野郎！
逃げ切れると思ってんのか!?
Pull over, damn it. You can't get away!
逃げ切れねえだと？
Can't get away, you say?
そう言われると 意地でも
逃げ切りたくなるじゃねえか！
When you say that, it makes me want to prove you wrong!
(警官)犯人は ﾀｰﾐﾅﾙﾀﾜｰ方面に
向かって 逃走中！
The suspect is heading for the Terminal Tower.
(警官)萌え萌え交差点を
封鎖されたし！
Request a block at Moe Moe intersection.
(警官)了解！
Ten-four.
♪♪～
The road, it's...
道が！
まだまだ！
We're not done yet.
♪♪～
Here goes...
よぉ～し！
Go!
があぁ～～っ!!
うぉ～～っ！
やったぜ～!!
(ﾊﾟﾄｶｰのｻｲﾚﾝ)
We did it!
ぎゃあ～～っ!!
(ｻｲﾚﾝ)
(みんな)うぉっ！
♪♪～
ﾍﾍｯ… ﾊ～ｯﾊﾊﾊﾊｯ！
やりやがった！
We did it!
(銀時/親父)ﾊﾊﾊﾊﾊ！ …ん!?
ぎょえ～っ！
子連れ～!!
Crap! A stroller!
(衝突音)
(大○郎)ちゃん｡
Pa.
My son and I walk a path of darkness and evil.
(拝 ○刀)我ら親子
冥府魔道に生きる者｡
We are in a hurry, so allow us our leave.
先を急ぎますゆえ
これにて ごめん｡
あの ｸｿ狼…｡
Damned wolf. Doesn't he know cars can't stop so quickly?
車は 急に止まれねえって
習わなかったのか！
≪(警官)いたぞ あそこだ！
There they are!
ｸｿ…！
おい おっさん！
Damn it!
Hey, Pops.
こっちだ｡
(神楽の寝息)
This way!
(警官)ｸｿｯ どこ行きやがった!?
Damn. Where'd they go?
(警官)捜せ！
遠くには行ってないはずだ！
Find them! They couldn't have gone far.
♪♪～
おい ｺﾗ！
いいかげん起きろって！
Hey, come on, wake up!
…くさっ！
It stinks!
なぜ ｵﾚに 手を貸すんだ？
Why're you helping me?
さぁな｡
I'm not sure.
(親父)おかしいじゃねえか！
ｵﾏｴらは 巻き込まれただけだ｡
It doesn't make sense. Now you're all wrapped up in this mess. And yet...
それなのに…｡
そりゃあよ➡
Well, yeah, but part of it is that I hate the police.
ｱｲﾂらが嫌いだってのも
あるけどよ➡
見届けてえのかもしれないな｡
あん？
Maybe I just want to see you through
特別な日ってﾔﾂをよ｡
your special day.
ﾌｯ｡
(親父)もうすぐ目的地だ！
We're almost there. Let's hurry!
(親父)急ぐぞ！
おぅ！
Right!
(お通)皆さ～ん！
(歓声)
Everybody...
(お通)今日は
お通のﾗｲﾌﾞに来てくれて➡
Thank you all for coming to my pooformance!
ありがとうきびｳﾝｺ～!!
(観客たち)とうきびｳﾝｺ～!!
Pooformance!
(お通)今日は
浮世のことなんて忘れて➡
Today, forget about your worldly cares, and just have fun, okay, necromancer!
楽しんでいってねｸﾛﾏﾝｻｰ！
(観客たち)ﾈｸﾛﾏﾝｻｰ!!
Necromancer!
じゃあ １曲目
『お前の父ちゃん ××』！
Okay, for my first song,
"Your Father is Bleep-Bleep".
聴いてくださいﾝﾄﾞﾒﾀｼﾝ!!
(観客たち)ｲﾝﾄﾞﾒﾀｼﾝ!!
Please enjoy!
♪♪『お前の父ちゃん ××』
♪♪｢××｣
なんだよ… これ！
What the hell...is this?
今 人気沸騰中のｱｲﾄﾞﾙ
寺門 通ちゃんの 初ﾗｲﾌﾞだ｡
It's the first live performance by today's up-and-coming pop idol, Tsu Terakado.
ﾃﾒｴ～!!
人生 なんだと思ってんだ～!?
You jerk. Is this your idea of life?!
ｱｲﾄﾞﾙのために 脱獄だぁ!?
You broke out of from prison for a pop idol?!
一時の享楽のために
人生 棒にふるつもりか？
You'd ruin your entire life for a moment's pleasure?
そんなんだから
ﾌﾞﾀ箱に ぶち込まれんだ ﾊﾞｶ野郎｡
That's the kind of the mentality that got you thrown in jail, you fool!
一瞬で 人生を棒にふった
ｵﾚだからこそ➡
It's precisely because I ruined my entire life for a moment's pleasure
人生には 見落としちゃならない➡
that I realize this an important moment that I can't miss.
大事な一瞬があることを
知っているのさ｡
しゃ～ 楽しもう！
Ｌ Ｏ Ｖ Ｅ お通！
So come on, let's have fun! L-O-V-E O-tsu-u!
L-O-V-E!
やってらんねえ｡ 帰るぞ 神楽｡
I can't take any more. We're going home, Kagura.
え～ もうちょっと
見たいんきんたむし｡
Aww, I wanna stay for more... son of whore.
影響されてんじゃねえ！
Don't let it influence you.
え～い もう…｡
ほとんど ｶﾙﾄじみてやがるな｡
This is like a cult.
なんか 空気が
あつくて臭い気がする｡
The air is rank with human stank.
≪お通！ ﾍｲ!!
L-O-V-E O-tsu-u.
(親衛隊たち)Ｌ Ｏ Ｖ Ｅ お通！
もっと大きい声で!!
(親衛隊たち)はい!!
Louder!
Okay!
(親衛隊たち)Ｌ Ｏ Ｖ Ｅ お通!!
L-O-V-E O-tsu-u.
おい そこ！
なに ﾎﾞｹｯとしてんだ！
Hey, pay attention! Shout it out.
声 張れや!!
(隊員)すみません 隊長！
Sorry, Chief!
おい いつから
隊長になったんだ？ ｵﾒｴは｡
Hey, since when did you become their captain?
ｵﾚは 生まれたときから
お通ちゃん親衛隊長だ！
I've been a captain of Otsu's fan club from the day I was born.
…ん？ ぎゃ～っ!!
銀さん なんで こんな所に～!?
Gyahh! Why're you here, Gin?
こっちが聞きたいわ｡
That's what I'd like to know.
ﾃﾒｴが こんな軟弱なもんに
傾倒してやがったとはな｡
You go for this teeny-bopper crap, too?
ﾃﾒｴの姉ちゃんに
なんて謝ればいいんだ｡
How am I going to explain this to your sister?
ﾎﾞｸが 何しようと勝手だろ！
ｶﾞｷじゃねえんだよ！
I can do whatever I like!  I'm not a little kid!
(母)ちょっと そこのあなた｡
You there.
(お通の母)ﾗｲﾌﾞ中に
ﾌﾗﾌﾗ歩かないでください｡
Please don't leave your seat during the performance.
他のお客様の ご迷惑になります｡
You're spoiling it for the rest of the audience.
すんません ﾏﾈｰｼﾞｬｰさん｡
ｵﾚが 締め出しとくんで｡
Sorry, Ms. Manager. I'll throw him out.
(母)あぁ 親衛隊の方？
お願いするわ｡
Oh, you're from the fan club? No problem, then.
今日は あの子の初ﾗｲﾌﾞなんだから
必ず 成功させなくては｡
Today is her first live show, so we have to make sure it's a success.
≪(親父)Ｌ Ｏ Ｖ Ｅ お通！
L-O-V-E O-tsu-u.
Ｌ Ｏ Ｖ Ｅ お通!!
あなた…｡
You.
We do-do!
いいぞ！ …ん？
♪♪～
(ﾌｧﾝたち)とうきびｳﾝｺ～!!
Everyone says it,
♪♪｢みんな言ってるﾊｽﾞなのに｣
♪♪｢出るとこ出ると 口つぐむ｣
but when the time comes, I just can't say it.
♪♪｢×× ××｣
Bleep-bleep! Bleep-bleep!
Otsu Terakado's second single.
(お通)寺門 お通 ｾｶﾝﾄﾞｼﾝｸﾞﾙ！
" Your Father is Bleep-Bleep," in stores soon!
(お通)近日 発売！
If you don't buy it, I'll rip off your mole.
買わないと
ﾎｸﾛ ひきちぎるよ！
♪♪～
(親父)そうか… ｵﾒｴが
お通のﾏﾈｰｼﾞｬｰやってたなんてな｡
I see.
So you're Otsu's manager.
The two of you, mother and daughter, made it this far.
(親父)親子二人で ここまで
のし上がってきたわけか｡
たいしたもんだ｡
Impressive.
Hearing that from you doesn't make me happy.
(母)あなたに言われても
嬉しくないわ｡
今さら よく
平然と 顔 出せたわね｡
I'm surprised you have the nerve to show your face after all this time.
(母)それに あなた
まだ服役中じゃなかったの？
Aren't you still supposed to be in jail? Why are you even here?
なんで こんなところにいるのよ？
(母)あきれた｡ 13年前から
何も成長してないのね｡
I've had it with you.
I can see you haven't changed a bit.
あなたが 好き勝手 生きるのは
結構だけど➡
You live your life however you please,
私たち親子のように その陰で
泣きをみる者がいるのを➡
but do you ever think about the people who suffer for it? Like your daughter and me?
考えたことある？
あなたが父親だってだけで➡
For no other reason than being your daughter, Otsu's had to endure so much.
お通は
どんなに つらい思いをしたか｡
(ｶﾒﾗのｼｬｯﾀｰ音)
((記者:お通ちゃん ｾｶﾝﾄﾞｼﾝｸﾞﾙの
『お前の父ちゃん ××』➡
Otsu, what's the key selling point of your second single, " Your Father is Bleep-Bleep"?
ｾｰﾙｽﾎﾟｲﾝﾄは どこ？
I'd say it's the hidden meaning behind the "bleep-bleep."
××という言葉の裏に隠された
意味っていうか➡
大人の事情みたいな感じのことを
意識してもらえると嬉しいです！
I'd be happy if you could appreciate its more mature implications.
(記者)明日 初めての
ｿﾛｺﾝｻｰﾄだよね｡ 意気込みを！
Tomorrow is your first solo concert, right?
How're you feeling about that?
一生懸命 頑張ります！
I'll do my very best!
(記者)そういえば お通ちゃんは➡
Come to think of it, Otsu, your mother is your manager, isn't she?
お母さんが ﾏﾈｰｼﾞｬｰなんだよね？
はい｡
Yes.
お父さんは ｺﾝｻｰﾄについては
どう言ってるの？
What does your father have to say about your concert?
父は…｡
My father...
この子の父親は死にました
13年前にね｡
Her father died. Thirteen years ago.
Is that true, Otsu?
そうなの？ お通ちゃん))
♪♪～
(母)あんな思いを
お通に させること自体➡
It's your fault for making Otsu suffer like that.
あなたの罪なのよ｡
消えてちょうだい｡
Just go away, please. And never come back.
そして 二度と
私たちの前に現れないで｡
(母)あの子に これ以上
嫌なこと 思い出させないで｡
Don't force her to relive painful memories like
(母)父親が人殺しなんて…｡
the fact that her father is a murderer.
(歓声)
♪♪～
ｶﾞﾑ 食べる？
Stick of gum?
そんなｶﾞｷみてえなもん
食えるか｡
Why would I want a kiddy thing like that?
人生 楽しく生きるｺﾂは
童心 忘れねえことだよ｡
The secret to enjoying life is to hold on to the kid inside you.
ま… 娘の晴れ舞台 見るために
脱獄なんざ➡
Well, busting out of jail just to see your daughter's big moment on stage
ｶﾞｷみてえなﾊﾞｶじゃねえと
できねえか｡
is something you can't do unless you're a childish idiot.
そんなんじゃねえ ﾊﾞｶ野郎！
That's not how it is, dumbass!
I made a promise to her a long time ago.
昔 約束しちまったんだよ｡
((♪♪｢ｱｲﾄﾞﾙになりたいよ｣
(笑い声)
I want to be an idol ~ La-la-la-la...
You must be my kid! A voice that awful has gotta be hereditary.
やっぱり お前も ｵﾚの娘だな｡
音痴にも程があるぞ｡
(お通)ﾌﾝ 今に見てな｡
Just you wait.
練習して うまくなって
いつか 絶対 歌手になってやる！
I'll practice and get better, and then one day I'll be an idol singer.
If you can become a professional singer,
(親父)お前が歌手になれるなら
ｷﾘｷﾞﾘｽでも歌手になれるわ｡
then there's even hope for the crickets.
(お通)うるさいわ ﾎﾞｹ！
なるっつったらなるって➡
Shut up, you meanie!
If I say I'll be an idol singer, then I will, I'm telling ya!
言ってんだろ！
(親父)おもしれえじゃねえか｡
How 'bout that!
もし お前が歌手になれたらよ➡
Well, listen, if you ever go pro...I'll bring a million roses to your first concert.
100万本のﾊﾞﾗ持って ｵﾚが
いの一番に見にいってやるよ｡
絶対だな？
You absolutely mean that?
Yeah, I promise.
あぁ 約束だ))
♪♪～
She's forgotten by now, I'm sure.
(親父)覚えてるわけねえよな
13年も前の話だ｡
That was thirteen years ago.
いや 覚えてても
思い出したくねえわな➡
Even if she still remembered, she wouldn't want to.
Not when she knows her pop's a killer.
人を殺めちまった
ﾊﾞｶな親父のことなんかよ｡
No telling how much she's suffered because of me.
ｵﾚのおかげで ｱｲﾂが➡
どれだけ苦労したか
しれねえんだからよ｡
She probably doesn't even want to see my face.
顔も見たくねえはずだ｡
I'm going back. Besides, I forgot to buy the roses.
(親父)帰るわ｡
ﾊﾞﾗ買ってくんのも忘れちまったし｡
迷惑かけたな｡
≪(神楽)銀ちゃ～ん！
Sorry for all the trouble.
Gin!
どうした？
What's up?
会場が大変ｱﾙ！ お客さんの１人が
暴れだしてﾎﾟﾄﾞﾝ発射…｡
Some guest went kablooey and freaked!
普通に しゃべれ｡
わけ わかんねえよ｡
Speak normally.
I can't understand a word you're saying.
いやぁ あの 会場にですね
天人がいたらしくて➡
In the concert hall. You see, there was an Amanto.
And to make things worse,
これがまた
やっかいなことに 食恋族｡
he was one of those Love-Cannibal-Clan Amanto that captures and feeds on the people he likes when he gets excited.
興奮すると 好きな相手を
捕食するという変態天人なんです｡
(新八たち)Ｌ Ｏ Ｖ Ｅ お通!!
L-O-V-E O-tsu-u!
(NO.49)うぅ… うぅ…｡
もう辛抱たまら～ん!!
I can't control myself anymore!
(悲鳴)
というわけで
報告に来たしだいでございます｡
And that's why I came to report it to you.
っていうか ｵﾒｴ なんで標準語？
Why're you speaking standard Japanese now?
♪♪～
(隊員)隊長！
会員NO.49が 暴走しました!!
Chief! Member number 49 has gone berserk!
あれも会員だったのか！
ﾏｽｺｯﾄ人形かと思ってた!!
He was one of us?
I thought he was some kind of inflatable mascot!
やめろ この野郎！
Stop it, you bastard!
Otsu!
(NO.49)お通ちゃ～ん!!
♪♪～
I'm so hungry.
(NO.49)腹 減った～｡
ｷｬ～～ｯ!!
Otsu. Become one with me...in my stomach.
お通ちゃん
ﾎﾞｸと一緒になろう… 胃袋で!!
いかん お通ちゃんが!!
Oh no, Otsu's in danger!
早く逃げるわよ お通！
Let's get out of here quickly, Otsu!
でも 腰が抜けちゃって…
どうしよう！
I can't. My legs won't move. What'll I do?
ふ～ん!!
♪♪～
だ… 誰だ あれ!?
Wh-Who is that?!
Otsu, run away. Quick!
(親父)お通 早く逃げろ！
(親父)ぐわぁ～っ!!
いけ～！
ﾎﾞｸらも お通ちゃんを守れ～!!
Go! We've got to protect Otsu!
(隊員たち)うわぁ～っ！
(お通)しっかり…｡
Hang in there!
しっかりしてください｡
気がついた｡
ﾑﾁｬするね ｱﾝﾀ｡
Ah, he's awake.
What kind of nut are you?  Pulling stunt like that?
こんなﾊﾞｶなﾏﾈして！
あの… あなた いったい…｡
Uh...who are you?
ただのﾌｧﾝさ ｱﾝﾀの｡
Just a fan of yours.
(NO.49)ぐおぉ～！
ぐおぉ～っ!!
ほわちゃ～っ!!
神楽ちゃん！
Kagura!
Came to help. Four straight weeks at the top.
助けにきてやったｱﾙよﾝ週連続
第１位！
何すんじゃ ﾜﾚ！
What're you doing?
That's what I want to ask you, Dining-kitchen.
それはこっちのｾﾘﾌだいﾆﾝｸﾞｷｯﾁﾝ！
銀さん！
Gin!
どいつもこいつも
ｼﾞｬﾏすんじゃないﾅｲｼｯｸｽﾃｨｰﾝ！
Stop getting in my way!
お前は そろそろ
退場しろやｷ肉食べ放題！
It's time you left the building. All the yakiniku you can eat.
でぇ～っ!!
♪♪～
ちょっと待ったぁ！
Hold it right there!
お通ちゃんは
ﾎﾞｸが守るんだﾙﾏさんが転んだ!!
Otsu, I'll protect you! The Daruma rolls!
ぐわぁ～っ!!
♪♪～
ｱｲﾂ…｡
That guy...
おっさん｡
Hey, old man.
♪♪～
そんなもんしか見つからなかった｡
That was all I could find.
100万本には及ばねえが
あとは 愛情で ごまかしな｡
It's not quite a million, so you'll really need to talk 'em up.
《ﾌﾝ… ﾊﾞｶ野郎》
Bastard.
There's no way she'd remember that promise.
《あんな約束
覚えてるわけねえだろうが》
♪♪～
《親父:だが この際➡
But at this point, does it really matter if she remembers or not?
覚えてようが覚えてまいが
関係ねえや｡
I'll keep my promise for myself.
ｵﾚは ｵﾚの約束を守ろう》
♪♪～
Otsu!
《親父:お通…➡
Take it all the way to the top.
しっかりやれよ》
Um...
(お通)あの！
next time, bring roses, okay?
今度は ﾊﾞﾗ 持ってきてよね！
私 それまで ここで
ずっと待ってるからさ…➡
Until then, I'll be waiting on the stage, Dad.
お父ちゃん！
♪♪～
よぅ 涙のお別れは済んだか？
Yo. Tearful parting go okay, pops?
(親父)ﾊﾞｶ野郎｡
お別れなんかじゃねえ｡
Idiot. This ain't a farewell.
また 必ず会いにくるさ！
I'll come back to see you again for sure.
皆さ～ん！ いろいろあったけど
仕切り直しよﾝの字固め！
Everyone! A lot's happened, but let's start over again! Figure-four lock.
(観客たち)４の字固め!!
Over again!
(お通)それじゃあ
聴いてください｡
Okay, please listen.
この曲を
私のお父さんに捧げます｡
I dedicate this song to my father.
『お前の父ちゃん ××』！
"Your Father is Bleep-Bleep."
Please listen. Indian Death Lock.
聴いてくださいﾝﾃﾞｨｱﾝﾃﾞｽﾛｯｸ!!
♪♪『お前の父ちゃん ××』
♪♪｢××｣
♪♪｢みんな 知ってるﾊｽﾞなのに｣
♪♪｢みんな しっぽり目をそらす｣
♪♪｢みんな 聞いてるはずなのに｣
♪♪｢出るとこ出ると 口つぐむ｣
《親父:今度は 胸 張ってな！》
Next time, I'll come with my head held high.
♪♪｢××｣
♪♪｢それは 魅惑のｲﾝﾋﾞﾃｰｼｮﾝ｣
♪♪｢それは 秘密のｲﾝﾄﾈｰｼｮﾝ｣
♪♪｢××｣
(お通)ｲｪｲ!!
[New Television Program]
In Kabukicho, Japanese hosts are on the decline
due to the emergence of good-looking foreign hosts.
But here are two men sporting their god-given gifts of blonde hair and butt-chin.
The mysterious vagabond, Kintoki Sakata,
and the former No. 1 host, the butt-chinned Shinpachi.
Having gained a female Chinese Mafia boss as a their patron,
the two men knife their way through the corrupt streets at night!
A new show, "Kintama" starts next week!
We're not even doing a show like that!
[Episode 1: "This isn't cosmetic surgery, I was born with a butt-chin."]
[The real next episode trailer as follows.  Stay tuned!!]
[Preview]
In Kabukicho, Japanese hosts are...
Gin! Please be serious and tell us about the next episode!
All right. Man, what a pain.
The next episode:  "Responsible Owners Should Clean Up After Their Pets."
Clean up after your pet, for Chrissakes!
＜ かぶき町では
ｲｹﾒﾝ外国人ﾎｽﾄ軍団の台頭で➡
和製ﾎｽﾄは
衰退の一途をたどっていた｡
が しかし ここに
持って生まれたﾊﾟﾂｷﾝと➡
ｹﾂｱｺﾞをもつ男が２人｡
謎のﾌﾟｰﾀﾛｰ 坂田 金時と➡
かつて ﾅﾝﾊﾞｰ１ﾎｽﾄだった
ｹﾂｱｺﾞ新八｡
ﾁｬｲﾅﾏﾌｨｱの女ﾎﾞｽを ﾊﾟﾄﾛﾝに迎え➡
今 ２人の男が
汚れた夜の街を駆け抜ける！
新番組
『金魂』 来週ｽﾀｰﾄ！＞
って そんな番組やらないからね!!